I will never
forgive you.
join the Eagles.
You need
to figure out
your own mess first.
Coach West.
We have received
reports that
you have bribed
referees and
used illegal
performance enhancers.
Your coaching license
is hereby revoked.
You're banned from
the NFL for life,
would you please
come with us?
What?
This, Ted, you
gotta talk to him.
If I can't coach,
I'll starve.
Illegals,
I don't even...
Please, please!
I'll do anything
you want,
I'll do anything.
People like you
are a disgrace
to the NFL.
Ted, wait! Ted!
You're gonna
fucking pay for this.
fucking pay
for this, Ted!
I'm Alan David Patrick West, Goddamn it!
Woah!
Hey, I heard
you don't really
have a place
to stay
after the divorce.
Yeah.
I was thinking
maybe,
if you wanted,
you could
stay with me.
For a little while.
It's up to you.
All right.
Well, I mean,
it's closer to
the field
anyways, right?
Exactly, it's way
closer to the field.
Yeah.